Mike Dawicki

Senior CIS Major with hands-on experience with web development and deployment, developing and maintaining both SQL and NoSQL databases and cloud computing via AWS. Check out my portfolio by going to mikedawickiog.github!

mikedawicki99@gmail.com (267) 566-7674 Ivyland, PA





linkedin.com/in/michael-dawicki

in

Education

James Madison University, Harrisonburg, VA

Major GPA: 3.56

Bachelor of Business Administration (B.B.A.) in Computer Information Systems (Anticipated Graduation May 2021)

Technical Skills

Languages - C#, Java, Python, SQL, HTML, CSS

Tools - Microsoft SQL server, Microsoft Visual Studio, Power BI, NetBeans

Frameworks - Bootstrap, ASP.NET

Project Experience

CIS Senior Capstone Project, James Madison University

Jan. 2021-Apr. 2021

- Developed an information system using an object-oriented approach for a client in the Harrisonburg community using C# and ASP.NET
- Major contributor to the system that was picked among the top two teams to present to a
 judge panel, CIS students, and CIS professors
- Responsible for the security of the system by utilizing the hashing algorithm PBKDF2 to encrypt user passwords in our database
- Responsible for both hosting the system on Amazon's Elastic Beanstalk as well as uploading the database onto Amazon's Relational Database Services

Amazon Web Services DynamoDB Project

Mar. 2021- Apr. 2021

- Created, manipulated and queried an AWS DynamoDB Database by using Python IDLE
- Gained relevant experience using AWS services including IAM and Amazon's non-relational database DynamoDB

Portfolio Website Jan. 2021

- Developed a portfolio website using HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap
- Deployed portfolio via GitHub Pages

Employment Experience

DSG Electrical Contractor, Electrical Apprentice, Morrisville, PA

Jan. 2016-Present

- Assisted employees in worksite readiness to ensure efficiency
- Presented the shop in a clean and orderly manner to strengthen sales

La Stalla Italian Restaurant, Busser, Ivyland PA

May 2018-Present

- Engaged with wait staff to handle all customer necessities
- Worked in a team-oriented environment to maintain cleanliness

Certifications

- Amazon Web Services Cloud Practitioner Essentials
- LinkedIn Learning: Introduction to Programming Using Python